dineshbakshi.com 2011-10-18

# Privacy Policy | dineshbakshi.com | IGCSE, A Level, IB Economics, Business studies, Accounting and ICT

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.

## Introduction

This policy covers the dineshbakshi.com's use of personal information that dineshbakshi.com collects when you use dineshbakshi.com. The policy also gives you information about cookies; dineshbakshi.com and third parties' use of cookies; and how you may reject such cookies.

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable the dineshbakshi.com and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. When using your personal information the dineshbakshi.com will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

## Visitor Information

During the course of any visit to dineshbakshi.com, the pages you see, along with a short text file called a 'cookie' may be downloaded to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.

Information supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better online user experience. For example: if on a previous visit you went to our forum, we might find this out from your cookie and let you use it without logging in.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows.

Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the dineshbakshi.com features. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

If you have set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse dineshbakshi.com anonymously. For further information on cookies please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

## Use and storage of your personal information

When you supply any personal information to dineshbakshi.com (e.g. for competitions, dineshbakshi.com services or dineshbakshi.com membership) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use those data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.

In general, any information you provide to the dineshbakshi.com will only be used within the dineshbakshi.com and by its agents and service providers. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to dineshbakshi.com or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on dineshbakshi.com, dineshbakshi.com can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of dineshbakshi.com membership you no longer wish to continue your registration as a dineshbakshi.com member. For safety reasons, however, the dineshbakshi.com may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of dineshbakshi.com services such as the quiz-maker for a period of six months. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other dineshbakshi.com services (e.g. competitions), that information will be held as long as is necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

If you are notified on the dineshbakshi.com site that your information may be used to allow the dineshbakshi.com to contact you for "service administration purposes", this means that the dineshbakshi.com may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for. For example, we may wish to provide you with password reminders or notify you that the particular service has been suspended for maintenance. We will not contact you for promotional purposes, such as notifying you of improvements to the service or new services on dineshbakshi.com unless you specifically agree to be contacted for such purposes at the time you submit your information on the site, or at a later time if you sign up specifically to receive such promotional information.

## How to see your cookie code

Just click on a cookie to open it. You'll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie.

## List of www.dineshbakshi.com cookies

This is a list of the main cookies that dineshbakshi.com sets, and what each is used for:

www.dineshbakshi.com cookie

Allows you to auto-login when you have registered to use the Forum.
